95: Guys!
3.1: Yeah?
95: I've got good news!
NT 4: What is it?
95: It's July 1!
NT 4: Huh?
2.0: What's so special?
95: Seriously?
95: 98 and ME are arriving soon, guys.
2.0: Wait, what?
95: You guys forgot!
NT 4: Ouch.
3.1: We should prepare something, then.
95: Of course!
3.1: We first need ideas, though.
NT 4: How about a party?
95: That sounds good!
NT 4: But where do we go?
3.1: Hmm...
3.1: What about Kernel?
95: Oh, right!
95: I didn't think about that.
95: What do you guys think?
NT 4: Yeah!
2.0: Definitely.
3.1: Sounds good to me!
95: Alright!
95: Let's go tell the others first.
2000: Hey, just came back.
2000: Woah, what's all of this?
XP: Just trying to build something.
2000: A computer it looks like?
XP: Yep!
2000: That's amazing.
2000: Did you get them off new?
XP: Of course!
2000: Great!
2000: Also, we haven't checked on 98 for days.
XP: Oh, right.
2000: Let's go check on him today.
XP: Can we invite him over here later?
XP: I need help building the PC.
2000: He might still be sick.
2000: We'll take him to the hospital if he still is.
XP: Alright.
XP: Now, we wait.
2000: Yep!
XP: Oh yeah, I just remembered.
XP: I still need to get a Windows CD.
2000: You haven't bought it yet?
XP: Nope.
XP: The store was closed when I went there.
XP: I went to the store pretty late, so yeah.
2000: Makes sense.
2000: Alright, let's go!
2000: Hey, XP.
XP: Yeah?
2000: Can you get lunch for us?
XP: Sure!
XP: Are you gonna get 98 meanwhile?
2000: Yep.
2000: Where are you going to get lunch?
XP: Millenium Market.
XP: Ubuntu sells great stuff there.
XP: Alright. I'll be somewhere here!
2000: See you later!
98: This is so boring!
98: Only resting for days...
98: Oh?
98: Just a second!
2000: Hey, 98!
98: 2000!
2000: Just came to check on you.
2000: How's things?
98: Well, tired. But I'm fine.
2000: Have you gotten better lately?
2000: You've been resting for days.
98: Not really.
2000: Have you checked with Whistler?
98: Nope. I should probably go check.
2000: Let's go check with him.
98: Yep.
2000: Here we are.
2000: Let's go in.
Whistler: Oh, hey guys.
2000: Hey Whistler.
Whistler: It's been a while.
Whistler: How have you two been?
2000: I've been fine. 98 feels ill, though.
Whistler: For how long?
98: About a week?
98: I haven't been to a hospital yet.
Whistler: Huh.
Whistler: Have you had this before?
98: I don't think so.
98: I don't really know what this is, though.
Whistler: It's alright.
Whistler: Let's head to the patient room.
98: Alright.
2000: Best of luck!
98: Thanks!
Whistler: I'll let you know once it's settled.
2000: Alright. Thanks for the help!
Whistler: No problem!
2000: Hey, I'm back.
XP: Hey!
XP: I've got some food ready.
2000: Yeah, I see fish and chips!
XP: You guessed it!
2000: Seems delicious.
2000: Although, 98 isn't here.
XP: Oh yeah, what happened?
2000: I took him to the hospital.
2000: He hasn't recovered yet.
XP: Huh.
XP: Hope he'll be fine soon.
2000: Yeah.
2000: Also, want to start eating?
XP: Of course!
2000: Delicious!
XP: What did I tell you!
2000: No wonder why you got the food there!
2000: Millenium Store is awesome.
XP: Can't agree more.
2000: On par with the coffee shop!
XP: You're kidding.
2000: Haha.
XP: Two different things!
2000: Yeah, literally.
2000: I hope 98 gets to eat this.
XP: I agree.
XP: This food is awesome!
2000: Oh, I think Whistler's calling.
2000 (On call): Hello?
Whistler (On call): Hey, you can come now.
2000 (On call): Sure, I'll be there in a minute.
2000 (On call): How'd it go?
Whistler (On call): Well, I don't really know what problem it is...
Whistler (On call): But he seems fine now.
2000 (On call): Huh.
2000 (On call): So you're not sure of what's happening?
Whistler (On call): Yeah, kinda.
Whistler (On call): But 98 seems fine now.
2000 (On call): At least that's good.
2000 (On call): Alright, I'll head there now.
Whistler (On call): Yep.
2000: Alright, I'll be back in a few minutes.
XP: Sure!
95: Well, we have arrived!
3.1: Let's head to the station!
1.0: Welcome to Gates Railways!
1.0: I see everyone's taking a vacation?
95: Yep, we're going to Kernel.
1.0: Cool!
1.0: Let me check the schedules.
1.0: Alright, we have one arriving very soon.
1.0: Do you want to book?
95: Sure, for all 6 of us.
95: The others are on their way.
1.0: Got it.
1.0: That'll be... zero dollars.
95: Haha.
1.0: Enjoy, monseiurs!
95: Merci!
1.0: No problem!
95: That was fast.
3.1: What timing!
Chicago: So, off we go now?
95: Sure we are.
95: Allons-y!
*Train announcement chime*
Train voice: Thank you for joining onboard with Gates’ Railways.
Train voice: Please hold onto the handrails, or take a seat.
Train voice: The train will now head to the next destination, Kernel.
95: We'll have to wait a while.
3.1: Yep.
Chicago: Well, while we're at it...
Chicago: I've got a game to show you guys.
3.1: What is it?
Chicago: It's Pinball.
95: Don't we already have that game?
Chicago: Yeah, but I modified it.
3.1: What's the difference?
Chicago: It supports 4 players now.
95: What?!
3.1: What did you just say?!
Chicago: You heard me!
3.1: That's amazing!
Chicago: Yeah, thanks.
95: So, how does this work?
Chicago: Multiplayer is all.
Chicago: 3.1, can you share your laptop with NT?
3.1: Sure!
95: This is something revolutionary.
95: Only within our realm, though.
Chicago: Obviously.
3.1: Let's start the game, then.
Chicago: I’ll set it up on your laptops.
Chicago: Give me a second.
Chicago: All done!
Chicago: Now, let us begin.
*Train announcement chime*
Train voice: The train will be stopping at the destination, Kernel, in 5 minutes.
Train voice: Please prepare to exit, and wait for the train to stop.
NT 4: We're almost there.
Chicago: Yep.
95: We don't have to rush, by the way.
95: The party's in a week.
Chicago: So we prepare, then
just have fun.
95: Pretty much!
95: I hope they'll like this.
Chicago: Yeah.
Chicago: Also, is anyone feeling hungry?
3.1: I think everyone is, haha.
95: Agreed.
Chicago: Let's head to a kiosk later.
95: Good idea.
95: Also, anyone excited for the new OS?
Chicago: I sure am!
3.1: 5 years, why wouldn't I?
NT 4: What took them so long, though?
Chicago: A development reset happened.
Chicago: I heard it wasn't going well.
NT 4: That’s unfortunate.
NT 4: I felt compelled with the project.
Chicago: Me too.
Chicago: But it's going well now.
NT 4: Oh, cool.
95: When is Vista arriving?
Chicago: I think Microsoft said January.
95: Oh wow.
*Train announcement chime*
Train voice: The train is now stopping at Kernel. Please don't forget your belongings.
Train voice: Thank you for riding with us at Gates’ Railways, and we hope to see you again soon.
95: Welp, we’re arriving!
NT 4: Party here I come!
Chicago: Alright, allons-y, monseiurs?
95: Ouais!
3.1 and NT 4: Oui!
98: I'm getting tired.
2000: You alright?
2000: It's been only a few minutes.
98: Yeah.
98: But my CPU is throttling.
XP: Hmm...
XP: I think it’s because you rested for days.
98: Huh.
98: I haven’t exercised for a long time.
2000: I’d say that’s why.
XP: If it gets worse, you should go check.
98: Of course.
2000: So… continue walking?
98: Can we go a bit slower?
2000: Sure.
XP: This place never gets old.
98: I haven't been here in months!
2000: Well, since we're here...
2000: Want to stop by the coffeeshop?
98: Yes, I need some coffee.
XP: Same here.
2000: Right then.
XP: Right, let's take a seat.
98: Yep.
Longhorn: Oh, hey guys!
Longhorn: You all here for some coffee?
98: Yep.
2000: We were going to my house.
2000: Just decided to stop by.
Longhorn: Ah, thanks!
Longhorn: So, regular coffee?
XP: Yep, just that.
2000: Same for me.
98: Same here.
Longhorn: Sure.
Longhorn: That’d be about 9 dollars.
2000: Sure, I'll pay.
XP: Sounds good.
2000: Right, I'm back.
2000: So, what’ve you guys been up to?
XP: I’ve been using my new PC for a while.
XP: It's so powerful it handles everything.
2000: Cool!
98: I’ve just applied to work part-time.
98: I missed out a lot, so yeah.
2000: Right.
2000: So where do you work now?
98: I work at Ubuntu’s market.
98: My shift starts on the weekends.
XP: Oh, cool!
XP: I actually went there a few days ago.
XP: Had to buy some food for the picnic.
98: Oh, haha.
98: I’m responsible for food restocks.
2000: Nice!
2000: How's the food there?
98: Super delicious.
XP: Sure is!
Longhorn: Here are your coffees!
98: Thanks, Longhorn!
2000: Thanks.
Longhorn: You're welcome!
Longhorn: I’ll be getting yours now, XP.
XP: Alright.
2000: Hey, by the way.
2000: A new OS is coming soon.
XP: Yeah, you told me.
98: Really?
2000: Yeah.
2000: It's called Vista.
98: That's a nice name.
98: I wonder where they got it from?
Longhorn: Alright, here's your coffee!
XP: Thanks!
Longhorn: You're welcome!
2000: So, you were saying?
98: I was just wondering.
98: Where'd they get that name?
2000: Not sure.
2000: But I reckon their employees, haha.
XP: What about the release date?
2000: I suspect it'll be in a few months.
2000: Microsoft announced it a few days ago, so...
98: That's exciting.
2000: I can't wait, honestly.
XP: It's been almost six years!
98: I know, right?
2000: Agreed.
2000: Also, how are you feeling now?
98: I feel refreshed.
2000: Ah, good.
XP: Shall we resume our journey?
2000: XP, my house is not that far.
XP: Yeah. I just call walking a journey.
2000: Fine.
2000: Ready?
XP: Yep!
98: Ready here as well.
2000: Alright.
98: Ah, another morning!
98: What shall I do?
98: Let me go get some breakfast.
98: Gonna check the fridge.
98: And, done!
98: Gonna turn on the radio.
Radio voice: -ou for listening to Microsoft Headlines.
Radio voice: The radio will be going over a few news today.
Radio voice: The first news is about support for the last two Windows 9x-
Radio voice: -operating systems, Windows 98 and Millenium Edition.
Radio voice: Support for the two operating systems will be dropping tomorrow,
98: Wait, what?!
Radio voice: and unfortunately, there is no option for paid extension of security updates.
Radio voice: Farewell, Windows 98 and Millenium Edition. Goodbye, 9x.